[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Italian car make was established on July 11, 1899 in Turin, Italy by Giovanni Agnelli?", "correct_answer": "Fiat", "incorrect_answers": ["Lancia", "Alfa Romeo", "Maserati"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Octopuses are known to kill sharks.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which United States President related a story about a murderous Bigfoot in a Wilderness Magazine?", "correct_answer": "Teddy Roosevelt", "incorrect_answers": ["Harry Truman", "U.S. Grant", "Billy Carter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cat breed is believed to have developed naturally in China. It has short golden brown fur with the so-called broken striped pattern and a large strong body.", "correct_answer": "Dragon Li", "incorrect_answers": ["Oriental Bicolour", "Korat", "Cymric"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Despite the myth that Chihuahuas were descendants of the royal dog of the Aztecs, it is also believed that Spanish trade merchants brought Chihuahuas to which of these countries?", "correct_answer": "Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["Venezuela", "United States", "Brazil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 61* and The Punisher actor was born Thomas Elliott III in Baltimore, MD. He studied at the Lee Strasburg Theatre Institute in Hollywood. He married actress Patricia Arquette in 2004.", "correct_answer": "Thomas Jane", "incorrect_answers": ["Mark Wahlberg", "Will Patton", "Nicolas Cage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, famous for starring in the Matrix series, plays Tres father in the 1991 film Boyz N the Hood.", "correct_answer": "Laurence Fishburne", "incorrect_answers": ["Yaphet Kotto", "Denzel Washington", "Danny Glover"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Captive raccoons are known for performing this vacuum activity.", "correct_answer": "Dousing their food", "incorrect_answers": ["Scratching their belly", "Playing dead", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robert Aldrich directed the war movie The Dirty Dozen.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "President Fords dog was named Freedom.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What disorder does Sams best friend Ifty have in the movie I am Sam?", "correct_answer": "Attention Deficit Disorder", "incorrect_answers": ["Dependent Personality Disorder", "Bipolar Disorder", "Autistic Disorder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the sea that borders the Netherlands?", "correct_answer": "North Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["Red Sea", "Black Sea", "Mediterranean Sea"]}]